pornhubcasino.com 2016-08-12

# Privacy Policy - PornhubCasino

## Privacy Policy

**1**   This is the official Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) of FN DATACLIVE CR (DBA PORNHUBCASINO).   
**2**     PHC takes all possible and reasonable steps to assure that personal information submitted to PHC is protected and held in a secure facility.   
**3**   Your personal information will be held and processed in Costa Rica, pursuant to its data protection laws, which may or may not be equivalent to the data protection laws in the country of your residence.    
**4**    PHC will review this Privacy Policy from time to time and reserves the right to make modifications and update this Privacy Policy at any given time.  PHC recommends that you review this Privacy Policy periodically.  Changes to this Privacy Policy will come into effect immediately upon such changes being updated on the PHC website by a prominent notice.  Your continued use of this website following such notification will constitute your acceptance of these new changes.  
**5**     By submitting your personal information to PHC you agree that PHC may: use of this data to create, manage and verify your account, provide you with PHC promotional offers, process any bets placed by you and comply with our regulatory duties.  You therefor agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.     
**6**     If at any time there is suspicion of illegal, fraudulent, or money laundering activities, PHC can and will share information about you with the relevant authorities, (example: the police, governing regulators, etc).  When you apply for an account with PHC, PHC may enlist and liaise with third parties to check your identity and age, credit worthiness and to prevent fraudulent activities or money laundering.  
**7**   All telephone calls may be recorded by PHC for training and security purposes.  
**8**   PHC may collect personal information from third parties including credit providers and financial institutions for the purpose of maintaining your account and conducting credit and other financial checks and you consent to our collection and use of your personal information for these purposes.   
**9**   PHC may use cookies to collect information for the above purposes following the customer's use of the PHC website.   
**10**   If you believe any of your personal information held by PHC is inaccurate or incorrect, you may request adjustments or new changes to your personal information by emailing:  [support@pornhubcasino.com](mailto:support@pornhubcasino.com) and provide PHC with your personal account details and the new information you wish to change on your account or by changing them yourself in the profile section of your account. It is your sole responsibility to notify PHC of any new changes to your personal information by sending an email to:  [support@pornhubcasino.com](mailto:support@pornhubcasino.com).   Should you wish to obtain a copy of your personal information that PHC holds or if you have any questions regarding the privacy policy or our business practices, please contact: [support@pornhubcasino.com](mailto:support@pornhubcasino.com) or check your profile page to see what is currently listed as your personal information. 

  *   PHC may disclose your personal information if: 
  * Required to do so by the authorities or by law;
  * PHC believes in good faith that such action is necessary to:

  1. Comply with any legal process served on us, this website or the gaming facilities;
  2. To protect and defend our rights of property; and/or
  3. Act to protect the personal safety of other users of the PHC website or the public;

    * To any intermediary gaming provider.
    * To any regulatory body, licensing provider or any authority.
    * To third parties who provide services to or on our behalf.
    * Third parties for the purposes of settling or making payment in connection with any bet or wager.
    * To any payment management company engaged by us to handle our payment collection processes to and from the players.
    * To any third party that purchases our company or our business. 

**12**      If you wish to obtain a copy of the information that we hold for you our customer service department will be happy to assist in this matter and they can be reached at [support@pornhubcasino.com](mailto:support@pornhubcasino.com).  This specific request can require a period of up to 30 days depending on the actual request.  
**13**      Your information is held in accordance with this privacy policy. To ensure regulatory compliance, your information is held for a period of time even after your account is closed.   
**14**       If you feel for whatever reason that PHC has not adhered to the above policy, please notify our customer services department, [support@pornhubcasino.com](mailto:support@pornhubcasino.com),  and we will address any valid issues as quickly as reasonably possible.

Information will be held and processed in Costa Rica, pursuant to its data protection laws, which may or may not be equivalent to the data protection laws in the country of your residence.
